One thousand brides. One hundred million dollars. Jimmie
Shannon is about to discover the true value of love.
The Bachelor is a comedy, romance film directed by Gary Sinyor.
Jimmie is seeing his single friends get married one by one.
He isn't too worried until his girlfriend Anne catches
the bouquet at his friend Marco's wedding.
Suddenly, his wild mustang days are numbered.
He finally decides to propose to her, but he sticks his
foot in his mouth and botches the proposal.
Being insulted by the defeatist proposal, Anne leaves town on an assignment.
After she's gone, he finds out that his recently-deceased grandfather's will stipulates that he gets nothing of
a multi-million dollar fortune unless he's married by 6:05pm on his 30th birthday: tomorrow!
Not being able to find Anne, Jimmie begins backtracking
through his past girlfriends to find a wife.
Jimmie, played by Chris O'Donnell.
Anne, played by Renée Zellweger.
Marco, played by Artie Lange.
Gluckman, played by Ed Asner.
O'Dell, played by Hal Holbrook.
Priest, played by James Cromwell.
The Bachelor is a 1999 American romantic comedy-drama fantasy film
directed by Gary Sinyor and written by Steve Cohen.
It is a remake of the 1925 Buster Keaton silent comedy film Seven
Chances and stars Chris O'Donnell and Renée Zellweger.
The film received negative reviews from critics and grossed
$36.9 million against its $21 million budget.
This film also marks Mariah Carey's acting debut.
The film explores themes of san francisco, california,
bachelor, remake, inheritance, wedding.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.